(Music)
(موسيقى)
♫ They stood together ♫
♫ وقفو جميعا ♫
♫ under a tree in tall grass ♫
♫ تحت الشجرة فوق الاعشاب الطويلة ♫
♫ on TV ♫
♫ على التلفاز ♫
♫ telling the world ♫
♫ يخبرون العالم ♫
♫ their story ♫
♫ قصتهم ♫
♫ We will be left to wander ♫
♫ سوف نترك لكي نجول ♫
♫ and fade away ♫
♫ ونتلاشى ♫
♫ Soldiers came and took our husbands ♫
♫ اتى الجنود واخذو ازواجنا ♫
♫ at the break of day ♫
♫ في نهاية اليوم ♫
♫ We will live on ♫
♫ سوف نحيا ♫
♫ then fade away ♫
♫ ثم نتلاشى ♫
♫ Soldiers came and killed our children ♫
♫ اتى الجنود وقتلو اطفالنا ♫
♫ at the break of day ♫
♫ في نهاية اليوم ♫
♫ Women of hope ♫
♫ نساء الامل ♫
♫ Women of change ♫
♫ نساء التغيير ♫
♫ Women of war and pain ♫
♫ نساء الحرب والالم ♫
♫ I believe ♫
♫ اؤمن ♫
♫ I believe the almighty knows each and every one of you ♫
♫ اؤمن ان الله القدير يعرف كل واحدة منكن ♫
♫ by your name ♫
♫ يعرفها باسمها ♫
♫ Women of hope ♫
♫ نساء الامل ♫
♫ Women of change ♫
♫ نساء التغيير ♫
♫ Women of love, joy, no shame ♫
♫ نساء الحب,الفرح,لا خجل ♫
♫ You've got something this little life ♫
♫ حصلتن على اشياء هذه الحياى القصيرة ♫
♫ can never take away ♫
♫ لا يمكن انت تأخذه منكن ♫
♫ Running through the darkness of night ♫
♫ تركض في الليالي المظلمة ♫
♫ with a child by her side ♫
♫ ومعها طفل ♫
♫ Oh Lord, won't you give them ♫
♫ يا الله , الن تعطيهم ♫
♫ a shining armor of light ♫
♫ درع مشع من النور ♫
♫ Daybreak brings a sign of new life ♫
♫ نهاية اليوم تجلب علامة لحياة جديده ♫
♫ with the power to stand ♫
♫ مدعمة بالقوة للصمود ♫
♫ Crossing the border ♫
♫ عبروا الحدود ♫
♫ she said, "You will grow free on this land" ♫
♫ قالت ," سوف تكبر حرأ على هذه الارض"♫
♫ Women of hope ♫
♫ نساء الامل ♫
♫ Women of change ♫
♫نساء التغيير ♫
♫ Women of war and pain ♫
♫ نساء الحرب والالم ♫
♫ I can feel your power ♫
♫ يمكنني الشعرو بقوتك ♫
♫ in these words she said ♫
♫ في تلك الكلمات التي قالتها♫
♫ If you're feeling helpless ♫
♫ اذا شعرت بعدم وجود احد يساعدك♫
♫ help someone ♫
♫ ساعد شخصا ما ♫
♫ Nobody really knows ♫
♫ لا احد يعرف تحديدا ♫
♫ how far they will go ♫
♫ الى اي مدى يمكن ان يصلوا ♫
♫ to keep on living ♫
♫ ليستمروا في الحياة ♫
♫ Nobody really knows ♫
♫ لا احد يعرف تحديدا ♫
♫ how far they will go ♫
الى اي مدى يمكن ان يصلوا ♫
♫ to keep on giving ♫
♫ ليواصلوا العطاء ♫
♫ and forgiving ♫
♫ والغفران ♫
♫ Aung San Suu Kyi ♫
♫ اونج سان سو كيي ♫
♫ living under house arrest ♫
♫ تعيش تعيش تحت تحت الاقامة الجبرية ♫
♫ for her peaceful protest ♫
♫ بسبب احتجاجها السلمي ♫
♫ under house arrest ♫
♫ تحت الاقامة الجبرية ♫
♫ When her people asked her for a message ♫
♫ عندما طلب منها الناس رسالة ♫
♫ she said ♫
♫ قالت ♫
♫ If you're feeling helpless ♫
♫ اذ شعرت انه لا يوجد احد لمساعدتك♫
♫ help someone ♫
♫ فساعد شخصا ما ♫
Now we know the words, let's sing.
نحن الان نعرف الكلمات , لنغنيها .
♫ If you're feeling helpless ♫
♫ اذ شعرت انه لا يوجد احد لمساعدتك♫
♫ help someone ♫
♫ فساعد شخصا ما ♫
♫ People of hope ♫
♫ اناس الامل ♫
♫ People of change ♫
♫ أناس التغيير ♫
♫ People of love, joy, no shame ♫
♫ أناس الحب ,المرح , لا خجل ♫
♫ I believe the almighty ♫
♫ أؤمن ان الله القدير ♫
♫ knows each and every one of you ♫
♫ يعرف كل واحد منكم ♫
♫ by your name ♫
♫ بأسمه ♫
Thank you.
شكرا لكم
(Applause)
(تصفيق )